<Publish>
	<!--Id must be set in order to update existed mod. it is not required for publishing mod for the first time-->
	<ModId Value="146643" />
	<!--Name of the mod to display to players-->
	<DisplayName Value="CS2 Metro Diagram" />
	<!--Short description of the mod-->
	<ShortDescription Value="Turn your city's metro network into a clean, readable metro map." />
	<!--Long description of the mod. Single line or multi line. Supports minimal markdown subset-->
	<LongDescription>
Turn the metro/subway network of your Cities: Skylines II city into a clean, readable metro map.

Beta.6 includes a read-only in-game preview. Open the metro-map button in the top-right toolbar to inspect the current city, refresh it, switch between geographic and schematic views, filter labels, zoom/pan, export JSON, or save the current SVG without leaving the game.

For the most complete official-style schematic map, export your city's metro network to JSON and open it in the free companion Windows Viewer. The Viewer can save SVG, PNG, or PDF for wallpapers, posters, printing, and sharing.

How to use:
1. Load a city and click the metro-map button in the top-right toolbar for the in-game preview.
2. In Options &gt; CS2 Metro Diagram, choose Auto / English / Simplified Chinese and an export folder.
3. Export JSON, then open the Viewer and click "Open Default Export" for the full schematic workflow.
4. Adjust the layout/size if you like, then save as SVG, PNG, or PDF.

The default map layout draws lines horizontal, vertical, or 45-degree, renders lines that share a track as parallel lines, and fills the canvas — the same conventions real metro maps use.

Download the Viewer and full source from GitHub:
https://github.com/Eriksas/Cities-Skylines-2-Metro-Viewer

Viewer download mirror (Baidu Netdisk) / Viewer 下载（百度网盘）:
https://pan.baidu.com/s/5RspPYzFb0dPoOE0aZu7d4A

Does your city's map not look quite right? Share your metro-export.json in a GitHub issue and the next version will be tuned against YOUR city.
觉得你的城市图排得不够好？把 metro-export.json 发到 GitHub issue，下个版本就拿你的城市调优。

Beta notes:
- Metro/subway only.
- Preview/export only; it never edits your city.
- The desktop Viewer remains recommended for manual layout editing and PNG/PDF export.
	</LongDescription>
	<!--Thumbnail-->
	<Thumbnail Value="Properties/Thumbnail.png" />
	<!--Screenshot, can be set multiple times-->
	<Screenshot Value="Properties/screenshots/01-viewer.png" />
	<Screenshot Value="Properties/screenshots/02-map-city-a.png" />
	<Screenshot Value="Properties/screenshots/03-map-city-b.png" />
	<Screenshot Value="Properties/screenshots/04-parallel-lines.png" />
	<!--Tag, can be set multiple times-->
	<Tag Value="Code Mod" />
	<!--Link to the forum post where the mod can be discussed-->
	<ForumLink Value="" />
	<!--Version of the mod-->
	<ModVersion Value="0.1.0-beta.6" />
	<!--Recommended version of the base game to use the mod-->
	<GameVersion Value="1.*" />
	<!--Dependency for the mod, can be set multiple times-->
	<Dependency Id="" />
	<!--Required DLC, can be set multiple times. Supported values are "Landmark Buildings", "San Fransisco Set", "Beach Properties", "Urban Promenades", "Modern Architecture"-->
	<RequiredDLC Value="" />
	<!--Change log for new version. Single line or multi line. Supports minimal markdown subset-->
	<ChangeLog>
Beta.6 - reliable framing and crisp zoom:
- All in-game previews now use a stable viewport, preventing tall, wide, single-line, and other extreme network shapes from escaping the map sheet.
- Fit-to-window keeps routes, stations, and labels inside the visible canvas.
- Zoom and pan now update the SVG viewBox instead of scaling a cached UI texture, keeping text and route strokes sharp when enlarged.
- Added regression coverage for horizontal, vertical, diagonal, parallel, crossing, large-coordinate, and real multi-line cities.
	</ChangeLog>
	<!--<ChangeLog>
	</ChangeLog>-->
	<!--External link, can be set multiple times. supported types are "discord", "github", "youtube", "twitch", "x", "paypal", "patreon", "buymeacoffee", "kofi", "crowdin", "gitlab", "gofundme"-->
	<ExternalLink Type="github" Url="https://github.com/Eriksas/Cities-Skylines-2-Metro-Viewer" />
	<!--Supported values Public, Private, Unlisted-->
	<AccessLevel Value="Public" />
</Publish>
